{
    "subject": "Afonso_I_of_Portugal",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Maud_of_Savoy",
    "human_readable": "Afonso I of Portugal is married to Maud of Savoy.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9774920344352722,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the marriage between Afonso I of Portugal and Maud of Savoy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.959754467010498,
            "question": "Is Afonso I of Portugal related to Maud of Savoy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9401280879974365,
            "question": "Who is Afonso I of Portugal married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9366940855979919,
            "question": "Was Afonso I of Portugal married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8804721832275391,
            "question": "To whom was Maud of Savoy married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8395205736160278,
            "question": "Was Afonso I of Portugal's wife from a different country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8217403888702393,
            "question": "What is the name of Afonso I of Portugal's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6650651693344116,
            "question": "What is the name of the king who married Maud of Savoy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6012430191040039,
            "question": "Who was the queen consort of Afonso I of Portugal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5990211367607117,
            "question": "Who was the queen of Afonso I of Portugal?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Afonso I of Portugal is married to Maud of Savoy.",
            "html": "yago_19562_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was the queen consort of Afonso I of Portugal?",
            "html": "yago_19562_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the king who married Maud of Savoy?",
            "html": "yago_19562_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Afonso I of Portugal's wife?",
            "html": "yago_19562_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19562_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19562_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19562_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19562_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19562_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19562_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19562_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19562_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19562_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19562_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents contain information that confirms Afonso I of Portugal was indeed married to Maud of Savoy, with multiple sources mentioning their marriage in 1146."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references confirming that Afonso I of Portugal was indeed married to Maud of Savoy. This information can be found in several documents, including `56.txt`, `1.txt`, and `97.txt`."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}